A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller papers, Speech Files, RG 5 FA434
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Speech Files, 1941-2004; 5; 38 document box(es)
  - 1974
    - Dedication of Charles I. and Lavinia M. Henry Memorial, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1974 November 19 (Box 12, Folder 270)
      Dedication of the 12th floor as a gift from Mrs. Harriet Henry de Steuch, daughter of Charles I. and Lavinia M. Henry.
    - Statement Regarding Nelson Rockefeller's Nomination as Vice President, Committee on the Judiciary, House of Representatives, 1974 December 4 (Box 12, Folder 271)
    - Office Christmas Party, Room 5600, 1974 December 19 (Box 12, Folder 272)
      Conditions Governing Access note
      Restricted material -- Material in the Rockefeller family collections which provides the names, correspondence or activities of living members of the Rockefeller family, and/or documents the net worth of any Rockefeller family members, is restricted from scholarly access.
  - 1975
    - Press Briefing, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1975 March 19 (Box 12, Folder 273)
    - Acceptance of Award, 75th Anniversary Celebration, United Neighborhood Houses, 1975 June 3 (Box 12, Folder 274)
      Award accepted "on behalf of the Rockefeller Brothers Fund and my family."
    - Dedication of Charles A. Lindbergh Bust, International Building, Rockefeller Center, 1975 August 13 (Box 12, Folder 275)
    - 25th Anniversary Ceremonies Marking Expansion of Grand Teton National Park, 1975 September 7 (Box 12, Folder 276)
    - Welcoming Remarks to King Olav V of Norway, 1975 October 2 (Box 13, Folder 277)
    - Awards Dinner, Cancer Research Institute, 1975 October 20 (Box 13, Folder 278)
    - Mrs. Rockefeller's Introduction of Dr. John H. Knowles, Off-the-Record Luncheon, Foreign Policy Association, 1975 November 19 (Box 13, Folder 279)
  - 1976
    - Official Opening, Lyndon B. Johnson Memorial Grove, 1976 April 6 (Box 13, Folder 280)
      LSR speech entitled "The Grove Concept and Its Fulfillment."
    - Supporters Luncheon, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1976 April 29 (Box 13, Folder 281)
    - Volunteer Recognition Ceremony, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1976 May 13 (Box 13, Folder 282)
    - Fort Lee Historic Park Dedication Ceremonies, Palisades Interstate Park Commission, 1976 May 15 (Box 13, Folder 283)
    - Retirement of David W. Walsh, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1976 June 15 (Box 13, Folder 284)
      David W. Walsh, former Acting President and Executive Vice President of MSKCC.
    - Dedication of Indian Art Traveling Exhibit, "Indian Pride on the Move," National Park Service, 1976 July 12 (Box 13, Folder 285)
    - Dedication of the Lila Acheson and DeWitt Wallace Children's Pavilion, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1976 September 21 (Box 13, Folder 286)
    - Cultivation Luncheon, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1976 October 6 (Box 13, Folder 287)
    - Presentation of President Lyndon B. Johnson Portrait, Southwest Texas State University, 1976 October 29 (Box 13, Folder 288)
  - 1977
    Folder 296, Box 14, listed under "1978".
    - The Unfinished Environmental Agenda: A Symposium, 1977 February 2 (Box 13, Folder 289)
    - Alaska Project, National Park Foundation, 1977 February 8 (Box 13, Folder 290)
    - Cultivation Luncheon, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1977 March 16 (Box 13, Folder 291)
    - Dedication of Percy L. Douglas Visitor's Lounge, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1977 March 29 (Box 13, Folder 292)
    - Dinner, Edward J. Beattie, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1977 May (Box 13, Folder 293)
    - Firestone Plaza Dedication, Princeton University, 1977 May 8 (Box 14, Folder 294)
    - Firestone Plaza Dedication, Princeton University, 1977 May 8 (Box 14, Folder 295)
    - Volunteer Recognition and Awards Ceremony, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1977 May 17 (Box 14, Folder 297)
    - Rosemary Hall Alumnae Award to Mrs. Laurance S. Rockefeller; YWCA Surprise Tribute for Mrs. Laurance S. Rockefeller, 1977 May 14 and 18 (Box 14, Folder 298)
    - Dedication of Arnold and Marie Schwartz International Hall of Science, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1977 May 26 (Box 14, Folder 299)
    - Acceptance of 1977 Distinguished Achievement Award, Wings Club, 1977 October 11 (Box 14, Folder 300)
    - Background Material for October 11 Speech, Wings Club, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 301)
    - Ribbon-Cutting Ceremony, Bridge-Parking Area, Lyndon B. Johnson Memorial Grove, 1977 October 12 (Box 15, Folder 302)
    - 45th Wedding Annniversary of Mr. & Mrs. John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Rockefeller Family, 1977 November 11 (Box 15, Folder 303)
    - Dedication of Abby Rockefeller Mauzé Pavilion, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1977 November 30 (Box 15, Folder 304)
    - Memorial Service for Dr. George Cotzias, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1977 December 14 (Box 15, Folder 305)
  - 1978
    - Volunteer Recognition and Awards Program, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1978 May 16 (Box 14, Folder 296)
      Folder 296, Box 14, was mistakenly placed out of date order in the original finding aid. Although listed among "1977" speeches, it belongs in "1978" and has been listed as such in AT.
    - Gene W. Setzer, Appreciation for 25 Years of Service, 1978 April 15 (Box 15, Folder 306)
    - Twenty Year Club Fourth Annual Dinner, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1978 April 18 (Box 15, Folder 307)
    - Gold Medal Award Dinner and Presentation to Mrs. Brooke Astor, New York Zoological Society, 1978 April 27 (Box 15, Folder 308)
    - Dedication of Leonard Parker Pool Floor (14th Floor), Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1978 May 2 (Box 15, Folder 309)
    - Capital Fund Campaign Honoring Brooke Astor, New York Public Library, 1978 May 18 (Box 15, Folder 310)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller's 70th Birthday Toast, Rockefeller Family, 1978 May 27 (Box 15, Folder 311)
    - Dedication and Opening of the Charles A. Dana Transplantation Unit, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1978 June 20 (Box 15, Folder 311A)
    - Memorial Service for Elmer Holmes Bobst, New York University, 1978 September 13 (Box 16, Folder 312)
    - Chairmen and Presidents Luncheon, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1978 October 3 (Box 16, Folder 313)
    - Acceptance of Distinguished Service Award, United Hospital Fund of New York, 1978 October 9 (Box 16, Folder 314)
    - Animal Kingdom Fund Luncheon, New York Zoological Society, 1978 October 12 (Box 16, Folder 315)
  - 1979
    - Testimonial Dinner for Nash Castro, Palisades Interstate Park Commission, 1979 January 11 (Box 16, Folder 316)
    - Dedication of William Paul Hoffmann Auditorium, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1979 April 10 (Box 16, Folder 317)
    - Farewell Reception for Charles Forbes, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1979 May 14 (Box 16, Folder 318)
    - Twenty Year Club Fifth Annual Dinner, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1979 May 17 (Box 16, Folder 319)
    - Luncheon Sponsored by Alcoa, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1979 May 18 (Box 16, Folder 320)
      Luncheon held at Duquesne Club, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania.
    - Japanese Businessmen Cultivation Luncheon, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1979 May 21 (Box 16, Folder 321)
      Remarks by Mr. Laurance S. Rockefeller and Mr. Yuichi Katoh of Tokyo, Japan, Senior Vice President, American Express International Bank Corporation.
    - Sixth Annual Volunteer Recognition Ceremony, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1979 May 22 (Box 16, Folder 322)
    - Animal Kingdom Fund Luncheon, New York Zoological Society, 1979 May 23 (Box 17, Folder 323)
    - Henry A. Kissinger Birthday Celebration, 1979 May 26 (Box 17, Folder 324)
    - Luncheon Sponsored by Xerox Corporation, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1979 June 27 (Box 17, Folder 325)
      Luncheon held at Xerox Headquarters, Stamford, Connecticut.
    - Presentation of Chair to Mrs. Virginia Kettering Kampf, Board of Overseers, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1979 July 17 (Box 17, Folder 326)
    - Sinatra at the Met Luncheon, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1979 July 19 (Box 17, Folder 327)
    - Dedication of the Nelson A. Rockefeller Academic Center at the New York College of Osteopathic Medicine, New York Institute of Technology, 1979 September 19 (Box 17, Folder 328)
    - Dedication of the Joseph Mullen Floor, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1979 October 10 (Box 17, Folder 329)
      The 10th floor of the Howard Research Laboratory was named the Joseph Mullen Floor.
    - Comments on Buddhism at Executive Committee, Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1979 October 31 (Box 17, Folder 330)
    - Tribute to the Memory of Arnold Schwartz, Arnold and Marie Schwartz College of Pharmacy and Health Sciences of Long Island University, 1979 December 12 (Box 17, Folder 331)
    - Chairmen and Presidents Corporate Development Luncheon, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1979 December 10 (Box 18, Folder 332)
    - Christmas Party, Room 5600, 1979 December 11 (Box 18, Folder 333)
  - 1980
    - Academic Convocation, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1980 March 19 (Box 18, Folder 334)
      Recognition of the donors of Chairs: Mrs. Brooke Astor, Mrs. Enid Haupt, Mrs. Virginia Kettering Kampf, and Mrs. Lila Wallace.
    - Dedication of Louise Nevelson Laboratory of Cancer Immunobiology, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1980 April 8 (Box 18, Folder 335)
    - Gift of Land to Princeton University, 1980 April 19 (Box 18, Folder 336)
    - Volunteers Recognition Awards Ceremony, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1980 April 23 (Box 18, Folder 337)
    - Frank Sinatra at 834 Fifth Avenue, Toast, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1980 April 29 (Box 18, Folder 338)
    - Spelman College Commencement, 1980 May 11 (Box 18, Folder 339)
      Includes Mrs. Laurance Rockefeller's acceptance of honorary degree during commencement, Laurance Rockefeller's remarks at Sunday night buffet, and Mrs. Laurance Rockefeller's remarks at Sunday night buffet.
    - Twenty-Year Club Sixth Annual Dinner, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1980 May 22 (Box 18, Folder 340)
    - Dedication of Harrison-Quinn Floor, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1980 May 29 (Box 18, Folder 341)
      Dorothy Thompson Harrison and Martin J. Quinn, Jr., Floor is seventh floor of the International Hall of Science for Cancer Research.
    - Farewell Dinner, Princeton University Board of Trustees, 1980 June 9 (Box 18, Folder 342)
    - Retirement of Dr. C. Chester Stock, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1980 June 26 (Box 18, Folder 343)
    - Andrew Heiskell Retirement Dinner, Toast, 1980 September 17 (Box 18, Folder 344)
      Andrew Heiskell's retirement as Chairman of the Board of Time Inc. Dinner held at the New York Public Library.
    - Welcome and Presentation to HRH Prince Philip, Duke of Edinburgh, New York Zoological Society Dinner, 1980 October 1 (Box 18, Folder 345)
    - Frank Sinatra Luncheon Remarks, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1980 October 2 (Box 18, Folder 346)
      Remarks regarding upcoming Frank Sinatra benefit concert at Radio City Music Hall, January 1981.
    - Hugh Morrow Retirement Meeting with Nelson A. Rockefeller Executors, Room 5600, 1980 October 6 (Box 18, Folder 347)
    - Annual Appeal Luncheon, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1980 October 15 (Box 18, Folder 348)
    - Dedication of Elmer and Mamdouha Bobst Medical Sciences Building, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1980 October 22 (Box 18, Folder 349)
    - Ground Breaking Ceremony, Mauna Lani Resort Hotel, 1980 October 28 (Box 19, Folder 350)
    - Alcoholism Meeting at 834 Fifth Avenue, Remarks, 1980 November 20 (Box 19, Folder 351)
    - Sinatra Dinner, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1980 December 5 (Box 19, Folder 352)
      Folder is missing as of July 11, 2012.
    - Presentation of Harold Willis Dodds Achievement Award, Class Day 1980, Princeton University; Launching of Princeton Campaign, Princeton University, 1980 June 9 and December 8 (Box 19, Folder 353)
      Harold Willis Dodds Achievement Award given to Robert Mason Thomas, Jr.; Princeton campaign launching includes introduction of William G. Bowen and birthday toast to Dr. Harold Helm
    - Installation of Dr. Paul A. Marks as President, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1980 December 2 (Box 19, Folder 354)
    - Fund Raising Visit to Tokyo, Japan, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1980 December 18 (Box 19, Folder 355)
  - 1981
    - Sinatra Benefit, Radio City Music Hall, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Institute, 1981, January 10 (Box 19, Folder 356)
    - Acceptance of Honorary Membership, Wings Club, 1981 January 14 (Box 19, Folder 357)
    - Rededication of The Lee Coombe Memorial Library, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1981 February 3 (Box 19, Folder 358)
    - Acceptance of "New Yorker for New York" Award, The Citizens Committee for New York City, 1981 February 11 (Box 19, Folder 359)
    - Ruth Woodward Visiting Professorship Dinner, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1981 March 11 (Box 19, Folder 360)
    - Volunteers Recognition Ceremony and Awards, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1981 April 29 (Box 19, Folder 361)
    - Air Shuttle Service 20th Anniversary, Eastern Air Lines, 1981 May 1 (Box 19, Folder 362)
    - Acceptance of James Ewing Layman's Award, Society of Surgical Oncology, 1981 May 12 (Box 19, Folder 363)
    - Twenty Year Club Seventh Annual Dinner, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1981 May 19 (Box 19, Folder 364)
    - Bob Hope Golf Outing, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1981 June 2 (Box 19, Folder 365)
    - Corporate Cultivation Luncheon, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1981 June 4 (Box 20, Folder 366)
    - Retirement Dinner Honoring J. Richardson Dilworth, Room 5600, 1981 June (Box 20, Folder 367)
    - Governor Winthrop Rockefeller Service at Pocantico, 1981 June 13 (Box 20, Folder 368)
    - Presentation of John D. Rockefeller Jr. Memorial Scholarship to Philip David Fink, 1981 June 14 (Box 20, Folder 369)
    - Sinatra Dinner Toast, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1981 July 9 (Box 20, Folder 370)
    - Acceptance of World Mercy Fund's Primum Vivere Award by Mrs. Laurance S. Rockefeller, 1981 September 25 (Box 20, Folder 371)
    - Annual Appeal Kickoff, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1981 September 30 (Box 20, Folder 372)
    - Wayfarer Ketch Dinner Honoring Retirement of Jack Fles and Randy Carpenter, Room 5600, 1981 October 2 (Box 20, Folder 373)
    - Dedication of Expanded Outpatient Facilities, James T. Murray Children's Pavilion, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1981 October 5 (Box 20, Folder 374)
    - Dinner Given by Ambassador and Mrs. Futscher-Pereira of Portugal, Inauguration of Meissen Swan Dinner Service from Nelson Rockefeller's Collection, 1981 October 7 (Box 20, Folder 375)
    - Unveiling of Plaque Honoring Laurance S. Rockefeller, Rockefeller Outlook, Palisades Interstate Park Commission, 1981 October 24 (Box 20, Folder 376)
    - Sinatra Benefit Corporate Luncheon, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1981 October 29 (Box 20, Folder 377)
    - Reception and Dinner Honoring King and Queen of Sweden at Rockefeller University, 1981 November 19 (Box 20, Folder 378)
      LSR remarks regarding Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center.
  - 1982
    - Sinatra Benefit at Radio City Music Hall, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1982 January 24 (Box 21, Folder 379)
      Artists included Frank Sinatra, Luciano Pavarotti, and George Shearing.
    - Cocktail Party Honoring Mr. and Mrs. Frank Sinatra at 834 Fifth Avenue, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1982 February 1 (Box 21, Folder 380)
    - Retirement as Chairman of Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center's Governing Board, 1982 March 24 (Box 21, Folder 381)
    - Birthday Toast to Brooke Astor, 1982 March 30 (Box 21, Folder 382)
    - American Cancer Society Reception and Dinner Honoring "Dynamic Duos" (Laurance Rockefeller and Mary Lasker), 1982 May 17 (Box 21, Folder 383)
    - Toast to United Nations Secretary General Javier Perez de Cuellar, 1982 April 26 (Box 21, Folder 384)
    - Princeton University Faculty-Alumni Forum, "Can the Private Sector Enlarge Its Support of Nonprofit Concerns?", 1982 June 5 (Box 21, Folder 385)
    - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center Award for Outstanding Support of Biomedical Science Presented to Laurance S. Rockefeller, 1982 May 17 (Box 21, Folder 386)
    - Cornell University Medical College Board of Overseers Meeting, 1982 May 19 (Box 21, Folder 387)
    - Dana S. Creel's 70th Birthday Party, Room 5600, 1982 May 24 (Box 21, Folder 388)
    - Retirement from The Alfred P. Sloan Foundation Board, 1982 June 15 (Box 21, Folder 389)
    - General Motors Cancer Research Foundation's Fourth Annual Awards Dinner, 1982 June 16 (Box 21, Folder 390)
      LSR served as Master of Ceremonies.
    - Press Conference on Proposed State Park (Rockefeller State Park Preserve), 1982 July 28 (Box 21, Folder 391)
    - Council of State Governments' Eastern Regional Conference, 1982 August 10 (Box 21, Folder 392)
      Conference held at Kykuit.
    - International Center for the Disabled Communications Awards Dinner, 1982 October 20 (Box 21, Folder 393)
      1982 Communications Awards Dinner Honorees: Clifton C. Garvin, Jr., Exxon Corporation; Laurance S. Rockefeller; and Danny Kaye.
    - Introduction of Mr. Douglas Dillon, Recipient of Voice Foundation VERA Award of Achievement, 1982 November 16 (Box 22, Folder 394)
    - Fund Raising Luncheon, New York Zoological Society, 1982 November 16 (Box 22, Folder 395)
    - Christmas Party and Celebration of 100th Anniversary of Family Office, Room 5600, 1982 December 17 (Box 22, Folder 396)
      Restricted Material - Material in the Rockefeller family collections which provides the names, correspondence or activities of living members of the Rockefeller family, and/or documents the net worth of any Rockefeller family members, is restricted from scholarly access.
  - 1983
    - Memorial Service for Nancy Hanks, Reading from Ecclesiasticus, 1983 January 18 (Box 22, Folder 397)
    - Opening of Mauna Lani Bay Hotel, Rockresorts, 1983 February 14 (Box 22, Folder 398)
    - Group Affiliates Citation Night, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1983 April 13 (Box 22, Folder 399)
    - Acceptance of Ira Allen Award, University of Vermont, 1983 April 22 (Box 22, Folder 400)
      Ira Allen Award presented to Mr. and Mrs. Laurance S. Rockefeller.
    - Introduction of Dr. Paul Marks, University Club Luncheon, 1983 May 3 (Box 22, Folder 401)
      Dr. Paul Marks - President and Chief Executive Officer of Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center.
    - Acceptance of Honorary Doctorate of Humane Letters, Marymount College, 1983 May 22 (Box 22, Folder 401A)
    - New York Blood Center Cruise, 1983 May 25 (Box 23, Folder 402)
    - New York University, Response Prepared for Milton Petrie Upon Receiving Honorary Degree, 1983 June 21 (Box 23, Folder 403)
    - Opening of Hudson River Situation Room, Hudson River Project, 1983 June 9 (Box 23, Folder 404)
    - Opening of Billings Farm and Museum, Woodstock Foundation, 1983 June 15 (Box 23, Folder 405)
    - Rockefeller Family Reunion, 1983 August 5 (Box 23, Folder 406)
    - Acceptance of Merit Award and Plaque, New York State Park and Recreation Society, 1983 June 28 (Box 23, Folder 407)
      Presentation of bronze plaque took place in front of Bear Mountain Inn.
    - News Release: Establishment of the Laurance S. Rockefeller Professorship in Philosophy at Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1983 September 2 (Box 23, Folder 408)
    - S. 1090 to Establish a National Outdoor Recreation Resources Review Commission, Testimony Before the Senate Committee on Energy and Natural Resources, 1983 September 23 (Box 23, Folder 409)
    - Dedication of the Nelson A. Rockefeller Center for the Social Sciences, Dinner, Dartmouth College, 1983 September 23-24 (Box 23, Folder 410)
    - Dedication of the Nelson A. Rockefeller Center for Social Sciences, Dartmouth College, Background Notes, 1983 September 23-24 (Box 23, Folder 411)
    - Dedication of the Nelson A. Rockefeller Center for Social Sciences, Dartmouth College, 1983 September (Box 23, Folder 411A)
    - "A Campaign for Princeton" Reception at Asia House, Princeton University, 1983 September 26 (Box 24, Folder 412)
    - YWCA Fund for the Future/125th Anniversary, Reception, 1983 September 29 (Box 24, Folder 413)
      Mrs. Laurance S. (Mary F.) Rockefeller was National Honorary Chairperson for the Fund for the Future national capital campaign.
    - "A Campaign for Princeton" Luncheon in Woodstock, VT, Princeton University, 1983 October 2 (Box 24, Folder 414)
    - Dedication of John D. Rockefeller 3rd College at Princeton University, 1983 October 16 (Box 24, Folder 415)
    - Dedication of John D. Rockefeller 3rd College at Princeton University, 1983 October 16 (Box 24, Folder 416)
    - Dedication of John D. Rockefeller 3rd College at Princeton University, 1983 October 16 (Box 24, Folder 416A)
    - Presentation of Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Portrait, Rockefeller University, 1983 October 17 (Box 25, Folder 417)
      Portrait in Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Hall.
    - Elmer Holmes Bobst Library 10th Anniversary Dinner, New York University, 1983 October 25 (Box 25, Folder 418)
      Evening also included the inauguration of the Elmer Holmes Bobst Awards in Arts and Letters.
    - "Tune In New York," First Annual Volunteer Awards Dinner Honoring John D. Rockefeller IV, 1983 November 9 (Box 25, Folder 419)
    - Retirement of Dr. Lewis Thomas, Chancellor, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1983 November 14 (Box 25, Folder 420)
    - Sinatra Benefit Kickoff Luncheon, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1983 November 29 (Box 25, Folder 421)
    - Rockefeller family: Christmas Party: Family Spirit, 1983 December 16 (Box 25, Folder 422)
      Restricted material - Material in the Rockefeller family collections which provides the names, correspondence or activities of living members of the Rockefeller family, and/or documents the net worth of any Rockefeller family members, is restricted from scholarly access.
  - 1984
    Folder 432, Box 26, listed under "1985". Event date: 1985 June 4.
    - Statement to U. S. House of Representatives in Support of the Awarding of a Gold Medal to Lady Bird Johnson, 1984 March 6 (Box 25, Folder 423)
      Resolution H.J.Res. 394, Joint Resolution "to provide for the awarding of a gold medal to Lady Bird Johnson in recognition of her humanitarian efforts and outstanding contributions to the improvement and beautification of America".
    - Corporate Night, The Mirror Theatre, 1984 March 22 (Box 25, Folder 424)
      Remarks also thank Sabra Jones and mention her birthday.
    - "The Land, the City and the Human Spirit," Symposium Sponsored by the University of Texas at Austin, 1984 April 12 (Box 25, Folder 425)
      Full title of symposium: "The Land, the City and the Human Spirit: America the Beautiful - An Assessment." See also Folder 426.
    - "The Land, the City and the Human Spirit," Symposium Sponsored by the University of Texas at Austin, 1984 April 12 (Box 25, Folder 426)
      Full title of symposium: "The Land, the City and the Human Spirit: America the Beautiful - An Assessment." See also Folder 425.
    - Kickoff Luncheon for Annual Appeal, Society of Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1984 April 25 (Box 26, Folder 427)
    - Statement in Support of H.R. 2837 and S. 1090 to Establish a National Outdoor Recreation Resources Review Committee, 1984 April 26 (Box 26, Folder 428)